Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Boating and Sailing
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records documenting boating and sailing
1920-2001
RU 986
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3
(3 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, reports, clippings, minutes, memos, and publications documenting boating and sailing at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Department of Athletics, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, reports, clippings, minutes, memos, and publications documenting boating and sailing at Yale.
Boats and boating; College sports; Sailing; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Records of the sailing team, 1926-2001; Accession 2006-A-008
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - Administrative records (reports, correspondence, clippings, etc.)
    - 1950-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 30)
    - 1980-2001 (Box 2, Folder 31 - 48)
  - Correspondence, 1956-2000 (Box 2, Folder 49 - 70)
  - Building committee, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Derby time trial records, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - History, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Organizational manual, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Public sailing classes, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Results, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Summer
    - 1971, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - 1993 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Summer: public sailing (includes slides), 1994 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Coaching review, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 82)